http://www.siouxfallsfcu.org/contact/about/join-sffcu/disclosures/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do, by downloading our privacy notice here.
Site Security
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Sioux Falls Federal Credit Union employs software programs to monitor network traffic.
Site Management
For site management, information is collected for statistical purposes. Computer software programs are used to create summary statistics based on interest, design specifications, and performance. No personal information, such as your name or address, is collected or used for this analysis. We collect no information which would identify you personally.
Information Collection
We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:
The Internet domain (for example, “xcompany.com” or “yourschool.edu) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our web site.
The date and time you access our site
The pages you visit and the result of the request
Other status codes and values resulting from the Web server responding to the request received.
When you send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a form that E-mails us this information, we use this information to fulfill or respond to your requests. We may store these requests to provide us with information for future improvements to our Web site. We may forward your E-mail to other Sioux Falls Federal Credit Union employees who are better able to respond to your request. Sioux Falls Federal Credit Union does not create individual profiles with the information you provide. Sioux Falls Federal Credit Union does not give, sell or transfer personal information to third parties, unless required by law.
PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT EMAIL MAY NOT BE SECURE AGAINST INTERCEPTION BY UNAUTHORIZED INDIVIDUALS. THEREFORE, IF YOU WISH TO COMMUNICATE SENSITIVE OR PERSONAL INFORMATION, YOU MAY WANT TO VISIT US, CALL US OR SEND IT BY POST MAIL.
Cookies Policy
Sioux Falls Federal Credit Union does not use “cookies.” (A “cookie” is a file placed on your hard drive by a Web site that allows it to monitor your visit, usually without your knowledge.) You can set your browser to warn you when placement of a cookie is requested and decide whether or not to accept it.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
Sioux Falls Federal Credit Union does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 without obtaining verifiable consent from their parents or legal guardians.  Our website is not designed to collect or use personal information from children under the age of 13.
If you have questions about SFFCU's website privacy policy please send us an email!
Connect with Us
Facebook
YouTube
Twitter
Pinterest
LinkedIn
Instagram
Contact Us
ATM Finder
You are now leaving the Sioux Falls Federal Credit Union's web site
By clicking on this link, you will be leaving the Credit Union's website and our Privacy Policy.
This web site is not operated by SFFCU. SFFCU makes no representations or warranties about any other Web site which you may access through this one.
When you access non-SFFCU Web sites, even though they contain the SFFCU logo and content regarding SFFCU's products and services, such web sites are independent of SFFCU and SFFCU has no control over the operation of non-SFFCU sites.
In addition, a link to a non-SFFCU Web site does not mean that SFFCU endorses that Web site or has any responsiblity for the use of such a Web site.
Cancel
Continue
